# **Erika Cannon**

804-572-3321 cannone.rva@gmail.com 513 Laurel St. Richmond, VA

### PROFESSIONAL SUMMARY

Hardworking individual with strong sense of work ethic, fairness, and passion for excelling in the workplace and outside of. Has friendly and established skills in customer service including professionalism and strong communication practices with 7 years of experience in restaurants and two years in a hair salon. Works well in both fast-pace environments and intimate social settings to build relationships with clients.

### **SKILLS**

- Eager to enhance skill sets
- Dedicated team player
- Organized multitasker
- Works well under pressure
- Positive attitude

- Meticulously clean
- Keen attention to detail
- Friendly and helpful
- Fast and efficient worker
- Team player

## **EXPERIENCE**

### Salt & Forge

Food Truck Operator/Line Cook

#### Richmond, VA

October 2019 - Present

- Responsible for self-managing daily food prep, working in a fast-paced environment with coworkers as a collective team
- Inspect and clean food preparation areas to ensure safe and sanitary food-handling practices
- Over-seeing food truck operations which include checking inventory, assessing the volume of product needed for various events
- Delegating tasks to employees
- Complying with a COVID safe, no-contact method of food pick up to ensure a successful and safe service

## Mango Salon

## Richmond, VA

Floor Assistant

December 2017- October 2019

- Aided stylists throughout the work day by greeting clients
- starting and or taking over hair services to ensure timeliness, and overall setting the salon to allow for daily functions
- Responsible for general cleanliness and aesthetic of the salon
- Making knowledgeable decisions regarding clients' needs, and building positive relationships with clients to ensure repeat business

# Lulu's

## Richmond, VA

Line Cook

June 2016- April 2018

- Cooked and served all meals per guest specifications
- Prepared and presented specialty food items for holiday banquets, weddings and corporate events
- Ensured freshness of food and ingredients by checking for quality, keeping track of old and new items, and rotating stock
- Kept up great food and service standards via team bonding and joint effort on the line

# **EDUCATION**

Virginia Commonwealth University

Richmond, VA

Fall 2014-Spring 2015